Inventory of the Norman Allderdice Collection
Hoover Institution Archives
- Series II (Box 49)
  - Foreign Languages Press/Publishing House, Hanoi and Beijing
    - "People of Indonesia, Unite ...,", 1968. (Folder 76: 36)
    - "People of the World, Unite, ...,", 1963. (Box-folder 77: 1)
      Collection of speeches and statements
    - "People of the World, Unite and Defeat ...,", 1966. (Folder 77: 2)
    - "People of the World, Unite and Struggle ...,", 1971. (Folder 77: 3)
    - "Philosophy Is No Mystery,", 1972. (Folder 77: 4)
    - "Political Work: The ...,", 1966. (Folder 77: 5)
    - "President Ho Chi Minh ...,", 1967. (Folder 77: 6)
    - "A Proposal concerning the ...,", 1963. (Folder 77: 7)
    - "Questions Concerning ...,", 1966. (Folder 77: 8)
    - "The Question of Independence ...," Mao Zedong, 1960. (Folder 77: 9)
    - "Rectify the Party's Style ...,", 1962. (Folder 77: 10)
    - "The Red Lantern,", 1972. (Folder 77: 11)
    - "Reform of the Chinese ...,", 1965. (Folder 77: 12)
    - "Refutation of the New ...,", 1965. (Folder 77: 13)
    - "Report on Adjusting the ...," Chou En-Lai, 1959. (Folder 77: 14)
    - "Report to the Second ...," Mao Zedong, 1968. (Folder 77: 15)
    - "Raise Higher the ...,", 1963. (Folder 77: 16)
    - "Reply to Khrushchov,", 1964. (Folder 77: 17)
    - "Resolutely Back Vietnamese ...,", 1971. (Folder 77: 18)
    - "Resolutely Struggle Against ...," Han-Chen, Nan, 1965. (Folder 77: 19)
    - "Revolutionary Dialectics ...," Shao Tieh-Chen, 1963. (Folder 77: 20)
    - "Revolutionize Our Youth," Yao-Pang, Hu, 1964. (Folder 77: 21)
    - "The Roar of a Nation ...," Chiang, Nan-hsiang, and others, 1963. (Folder 77: 22)
    - "Scaling Peaks in Medical ...,", 1972. (Folder 77: 23)
    - "Second Session of the ...,", 1958. (Folder 77: 24)
    - "Selected Essays on the ...,", 1971. (Folder 77: 25)
    - "Self-Reliance and ...,", 1963. (Folder 77: 26)
    - "Seven Letters Exchanged ...,", 1964. (Folder 77: 27)
      Collection of letters
    - "Signal Victory of the ...,", 1970. (Folder 77: 28)
  - Wenzi-Gaige Publishing House--"Simple Chinese Conversation,", 1958. (Folder 77: 29)
  - Foreign Languages Press/Publishing House, Hanoi and Beijing
    - "The Sino-Indian Boundary ...,", 1965. (Folder 77: 30)
    - "Sino-Soviet Alliance ...,", 1960. (Folder 77: 31)
    - "Sino-U.S. Joint Communiqué,", 1972. (Folder 77: 32)
    - "Solemn Pledge of the Thirty ...,", 1965. (Folder 77: 33)
    - "Some Questions Concerning Methods ...," Mao Zedong, 1962. (Box-folder 78: 1)
    - "Some Questions Concerning the ...," Duan, Le, 1964. (Folder 78: 2)
    - "South Viet Nam a Great ...,", 1967. (Folder 78: 3)
    - "Special War: An Outgrowth ...," Nguyen Van Thieu, 1965. (Folder 78: 4)
    - "Speech at the Allarcham ...," Peng Chen, 1965. (Folder 78: 5)
    - "Speech at the Party School ...," Wilcox, V. G., 1964. (Folder 78: 6)
    - "Speech," Kuan-Hua, Chiao, 1973. (Folder 78: 7)
    - "Speeches Welcoming the ...,", 1971. (Folder 78: 8)
    - "Statements by Mao Zedong,", 1964. (Folder 78: 9)
    - "Statement Calling on the ...," Mao Zedong, 1964. (Folder 78: 10)
    - "Statement of Ten Central ...,", 1964. (Folder 78: 11)
    - "Statement of the Government ...,", 1969. (Folder 78: 12)
    - "Statement on the March ...,", 1965. (Folder 78: 13)
    - "The Story of the Modern ... Taking Tiger ...,", 1972. (Folder 78: 14)
    - "Strategy: One Against ...," Li, Tso-Peng, 1966. (Folder 78: 15)
    - "Strive for the Victory ...," Njoto, 1965. (Folder 78: 16)
    - "Strive to Build a ...,", 1972. (Folder 78: 17)
    - "A Struggle Between Two ...," Fan Hsiu-Chu, 1965. (Folder 78: 18)
    - "The Struggle between ...,", 1968. (Folder 78: 19)
    - "The Struggle between ...,", 1963. (Folder 78: 20)
    - "The Struggle in the ...," Mao Zedong, 1968. (Folder 78: 21)
    - "Summary of the Forum on ...,", 1968. (Folder 78: 22)
    - "Support the Dominican ...,", 1965. (Folder 78: 23)
    - "Support the Just and ...,", 1960. (Folder 78: 24)
    - "Support the Just Stand ...,", 1960. (Folder 78: 25)
    - "Support the Patriotic and ...,", 1960. (Folder 78: 26)
    - "Support the People"
      - I, 1965. (Folder 78: 27)
      - II, 1965. (Folder 78: 28)
      - III, 1965. (Folder 78: 29)
      - IV, 1965. (Folder 78: 30)
    - "Tachai--Standard Bearer ...,", 1972. (Folder 78: 31)
    - "Taching--Red Banner on ...,", 1972. (Folder 78: 32)
    - "Taking the Bandits' ...,", 1968. (Folder 78: 33)
    - "The Tenth National Congress ...,", 1973. (Folder 78: 34)
      Collection of documents
    - "Theory and Practice ...,", 1965. (Folder 78: 35)
    - "Thwart the Maneuvres ...,", 1964. (Folder 78: 36)
    - "To Find Men Really Great ...,", 1971. (Folder 78: 37)
    - "Training Successors for ...,", 1965. (Box-folder 79: 1)
    - "The True Story of Ah Q ...," Lu Hsun, 1972. (Folder 79: 2)
    - "The Truth about How the ...,", 1963. (Folder 79: 3)
    - "Two Policies and Programs ...," Mao Zedong, 1960. (Folder 79: 4)
      Miscellaneous speeches and articles
    - "Unite to Win Still ...,", 1972. (Folder 79: 5)
    - "U.S. Aggression Has No Bounds ...,", 1966. (Folder 79: 6)
      Articles and statements
    - "Vice-Premier Chen Yi ...,", 1966. (Folder 79: 7)
    - "Vicious Motive, Despicable ...,", 1974. (Folder 79: 8)
      Comments
    - "A Victory for the Five ...,", 1960. (Folder 79: 9)
    - "Viet Nam and the Failure ...,", 1968. (Folder 79: 10)
      Official documents
    - "We Must Learn to Do ...," Mao Zedong, 1965. (Folder 79: 11)
    - "The Whole Country Should ...,", 1966. (Folder 79: 12)
    - "Who Will Win in South ...," Chi Thanh Nguyen, 1963. (Folder 79: 13)
    - "Why Is It that Red Political ...," Mao Zedong, 1968. (Folder 79: 14)
    - "Why Khrushchov Fell,", 1964. (Folder 79: 15)
    - "The Working Class Must ...," Yao, Wen-Yuan, 1968. (Folder 79: 16)
    - "ApBac: Major Battles ...," Le Hong Linh, and others, 1965. (Folder 79: 17)
    - "After Political Failure the ...,", 1966. (Folder 79: 18)
    - "Against U.S. Aggression ...,", 1965. (Folder 79: 19)
    - "Forward! Final Victory ...,", 1968. (Folder 79: 20)
    - "Forward under the Glorious ...," Duan, Le, 1967. (Folder 79: 21)
    - "In the Liberated Zone ...,", 1968. (Folder 79: 22)
    - "Let us Hold Aloft the ...,", 1965. (Folder 79: 23)
    - "The Narrow Strip of Land," Mai Nam, Tran, 1969. (Folder 79: 24)
    - "North Vietnam against U.S. ...," Thu, Hai, 1967. (Folder 79: 25)
    - "On the 17th Parallel,", 1965. (Folder 79: 26)
    - "President Hô-Chi-Minh ...,", 1966. (Folder 79: 27)
      Biography
    - "Scenes of the General ...,", 1968. (Folder 79: 28)
    - "Some Aspects of Guerilla ...," Hoang, Van Thai, 1965. (Folder 79: 29)
      Collection of short stories
    - "South Vietnam Initial ...,", 1967. (Folder 79: 30)
      Communiqué
    - "South Vietnam: U.S. Defeat ...," Van Tien, Dung, 1967. (Folder 79: 31)
    - "Vietnamese and Teaching ...,", 1968. (Box-folder 80: 1)
    - "The Vietnamese People on ...," Nguyen Van Vinh, 1966. (Folder 80: 2)
    - "The Vietnamese Problem," Luu Quy Ky, 1967. (Folder 80: 3)
    - "We Will Win,", 1965. (Folder 80: 4)
  - Foreign Language Publishing House, Moscow
    - "Advancing to Communism,", 1951. (Folder 80: 5)
      Notes of a pioneer in collective farming in Ukraine
    - "A World We do not See," Potkov, Lev, 1957. (Folder 80: 6)
  - Foreign Language Publishing House, Korea--"A Foolish Ruler,", 1975. (Folder 80: 7)
    Reports from South Korea
  - Foreign Language Publishing House, Moscow--"Stalin and the ...," Andreyev, A., 1950. (Folder 80: 8)
  - Foreign Language Publishing House, Korea
    - "In the Revolutionary ...," Kim, Gum Sam, 1976. (Folder 80: 9)
    - "Answers to ...," Kim Il Sung, 1975. (Folder 80: 10)
    - "Answers to ...," Kim Il Sung, 1975. (Folder 80: 11)
    - "Let us Further Strengthen ...," Kim Il Sung, 1977. (Folder 80: 12)
    - "On the Land Law" and "Let us Shatter ...," Kim Il Sung, 1977-1983. (Folder 80: 13)
    - "The Land Law of ...,", 1977. (Folder 80: 14)
    - "On the Occasion ...," Kim Il Sung, 1975. (Folder 80: 15)
  - Foreign Language Publishing House, Moscow--"We are Indebted ...," Kosygin, A., 1950. (Folder 80: 16)
  - Foreign Language Publishing House, Hanoi
    - "On the Socialist Revolution ...," Volume I, Duan, Le, 1965. (Folder 80: 17)
    - "Letters from South Vietnam,", 1963. (Folder 80: 18)
    - "On the Socialist Revolution ...," Volume II, Duan, Le, 1965. (Folder 80: 19)
  - Foreign Language Publishing House, Korea
    - Kim Il Sung
      - "For the Efficient Administration ...,", 1977. (Folder 80: 20)
      - "On Further Developing the ...,", 1976. (Folder 80: 21)
      - "On Introducing ...,", 1975. (Folder 80: 22)
      - "On Progressive Democracy,", 1976. (Folder 80: 23)
      - "On the Road Followed ...,", 1978. (Folder 80: 24)
      - "To Spread and Develop ...,", 1976. (Folder 80: 25)
    - Li, Ryong
      - "Traitor Pak Jung,", 1975. (Folder 80: 26)
  - Foreign Language Publishing House, Moscow
    - "Comrade Stalin ...," Malenkov, G., 1950. (Folder 80: 27)
    - "Speech at an Election Meeting ...," Molotov, V. M., 1950. (Folder 80: 28)
  - Foreign Language Publishing House, Korea
    - "North-South Dialogue ...,", 1976. (Folder 80: 29)
    - Kim Il Sung
      - "On Further Developing ...,", 1976. (Folder 80: 30)
      - "On Preparing for the Great Event ...,", 1976. (Folder 80: 31)
      - "On Progressive Democracy,", 1976. (Box-folder 81: 1)
      - "On the Occasion of Founding ...,", 1976. (Folder 81: 2)
      - "The Tasks of Communists ...,", 1976. (Folder 81: 3)
    - "The Truth of the Panmunjom Incident,", 1976. (Folder 81: 4)
    - "To Spread and Develop ...," Kim Il Sung, 1976. (Folder 81: 5)
  - Foreign Language Publishing House, Moscow
    - "Comrade Stalin ...," Shvernik, N., 1950. (Folder 81: 6)
    - "A. I. Herzen: Great Russian Thinker ...," Teryaev, G., 1954. (Folder 81: 7)
    - "Draft of Model Rules ...," Moskatov, P. G., 1938. (Folder 81: 8)
    - "Moscow's Multi-Storey Buildings," Vlasov, A., 1954. (Folder 81: 9)
  - Foreign Policy Association--Headline Series--Pamphlets
    - "Middle East in ...," Baldwin, Hanson W., 1957 (Folder 81: 10)
    - "Our China Policy ...," Barnett, A. Doak, 1971 (Folder 81: 11)
    - "Disarmament ...," Bloomfield, Lincoln P., 1968 (Folder 81: 12)
    - "Only by Understanding ...," Carr, William G., 1945 (Folder 81: 13)
    - "A Peace that Pays," Brockway, Thomas P., 1944 (Folder 81: 14)
    - "Toward a Dynamic America ...," Childs, Marquis W. and William T. Stone, 1941 (Folder 81: 15)
    - "The New Japan," Dangerfield, Royden, 1953 (Folder 81: 16)
    - "On the Threshold ..." and "After Victory ...," Dean, Vera Micheles, 1944-1945 (Folder 81: 17)
    - Emeny, Brooks
      - "Mainsprings of World Politics,", 1956 (Folder 81: 18)
      - "Mainsprings of World ...,", 1943 (Folder 81: 19)
    - "Vietnam: Is Victory ...,", 1964 (Folder 81: 20)
    - "War on the Short ..., Graves," Harold N., Jr., 1941 (Folder 81: 21)
    - "The New United ...," Gross, Ernest A., 1957 (Folder 81: 22)
    - "America's Battlefronts ...," Gruin, Frederick, 1943 (Folder 81: 23)
    - "Indonesia: Guided ...," Hanna, Willard A., 1961 (Folder 81: 24)
    - "Rising Sun," Hart, Richard, 1946 (Folder 81: 25)
    - "Decisions ...,", 1957 (Folder 81: 26)
    - "Europe's Homeless ...," Hoehler, Fred K., 1945 (Folder 81: 27)
    - "Skyways of Tomorrow," Hershey, Burnet, 1944 (Folder 81: 28)
    - "Mexico: Land ...," Holmes, Henry Alfred, and Lula Thomas, 1952 (Folder 81: 29)
    - "The Changing ...," Johnstone, William C., 1943. (Folder 81: 30)
  - Foreign Language Publishing House, Korea (Box 82)
    - Kim Il Sung
      - "On Introducing New ...,", 1975. (Folder 82: 1)
      - "Talk with the ...,", 1976 (Folder 82: 2)
    - "Our Stake ...," Lubin, Isador, and Forrest D. Murden Jr., 1954 (Folder 82: 3)
    - "France: Crossroads ...," Miller, Helen Hill, 1944 (Folder 82: 4)
    - "New Era in Eastern ...," Raymond, Jack, 1957 (Folder 82: 5)
    - "The Population Explosion," Sax, Karl, 1956 (Folder 82: 6)
    - "Restless India," Rosinger, Lawrence K., 1946 (Folder 82: 7)
    - "The Arctic in ...," Stefansson, Vilhjalmur, 1945 (Folder 82: 8)
    - "European Jigsaw," Valkenburg, Samuel Van, 1945 (Folder 82: 9)
    - "Whose Promised Lands?" Valkenburg, Samuel Van, 1946 (Folder 82: 10)
    - "Vietnam: Vital Issues in the Great Debate,", 1966 (Folder 82: 11)
    - "The New Britain," Webb, Robert K., 1955 (Folder 82: 12)
  - Foreign Relations of the United States, 1945. (Folder 82: 13)
  - "A Synthesis at the 1st Fortune Round Table,", 1939. (Folder 82: 14)
  - Forum Publishing Company
    - "Federal Reserve Corporation," McFadden, Louis T., 1934. (Folder 82: 15)
      Remarks in Congress
    - "What's Wrong in Washington?" Vennard, Wickliffe B., Sr., 1957-1958. (Folder 82: 16-17)
    - "The Enemy Within," Vennard, Wickliffe B., Sr., undated. (Folder 82: 18)
    - "The National Forum ...," White, William Russell, undated. (Folder 82: 19)
  - Forward Movement Publications
    - "Instructions in the Life of Prayer,", undated. (Folder 82: 20)
    - "Prayers for Lent," Bone, Robert H., 1973. (Folder 82: 21)
  - Foster, Julian, "None Dare Call It Reason,", 1964. (Folder 82: 22)
  - Foundation for Economic Education
    - "The Freedom to Move," Cooley, Oscar W., and Paul Poirot, 1951. (Folder 82: 23)
    - "How the Heavy Hand ...," Swearingen, John E., 1962. (Folder 82: 24)
  - Foundation Fellowship
    - Pelley, William Dudley
      - "How to Read the ...,", undated. (Folder 82: 25)
      - "The Three Strange Origins of Mortal Souls,", undated. (Folder 82: 26)
        Sermon?
  - Foundation for Christian Economics
    - "For What Are We Searching?", 1932?. (Folder 82: 27)
    - "Health: How the Overloaded Mind ...,", undated. (Folder 82: 28)
      Program of services for the thirty-fifth assembly
    - "Vibration: How it Affects Materialization,", undated. (Folder 82: 29)
      Program of services for thirty-third assembly
    - "Vibration: The Missing Link ...,", undated. (Folder 82: 30)
      Program of services for thirty-second assembly
    - "Vibration in the Body: How it Acts on Mind ...,", undated. (Folder 82: 31)
      Program of services for 34th Assembly
  - Foundation Fellowship--"Why the Hebrews ...,", undated. (Folder 82: 32)
    Thirtieth lecture lesson
  - Foundation for Economic Education (Box 83)
    - "The Law," Bastiat, Frederic, 1964. (Folder 83: 1)
    - "Human Rights ...," Clinchy, Russell J., 1952. (Folder 83: 2)
    - "The Tariff Idea," Curtiss, W. M., 1953. (Folder 83: 3)
    - "No Vacancies, De Jouvenel," Bertrand, 1948. (Folder 83: 4)
    - "The Growth of an Idea: ...,", 1954. (Folder 83: 5)
    - "On Search of Peace," Harper, F. A., 1951. (Folder 83: 6)
    - "Morals and the Welfare-State" and "Agriculture's Sacred Seventh," Harper, F. A., 1951-1954. (Folder 83: 7)
    - "The Personal Practice of Freedom, Lipscomb, Ed, 1952. (Folder 83: 8)
    - "The Lengthening Shadow of Government," Opitz, Edmund A., 1954. (Folder 83: 9)
    - "Competition? Yes, but--," Phillips, Charles F., 1955. (Folder 83: 10)
    - "Bargaining," Poirot, Paul L., 1953. (Folder 83: 11)
    - "Public Housing," Poirot, Paul L., 1954. (Folder 83: 12)
    - "Social Security," Poirot, Paul L., 1954. (Folder 83: 13)
    - Read, Leonard E.
      - "Conscience on the Battlefield,", 1951. (Folder 83: 14)
      - "Outlook for Freedom,", 1951. (Folder 83: 15)
      - "Students of Liberty,", 1950. (Folder 83: 16)
      - "Two Ways to Stop Strike,", 1951. (Folder 83: 17)
      - "Victims of Social Leveling,", 1953. (Folder 83: 18)
      - "Report on Freedom,", 1954-1955. (Folder 83: 19)
    - "Equality and Security," Russell, Dean, 1952. (Folder 83: 20)
    - "My Freedom Depends on Yours," Russell, Dean, 1953. (Folder 83: 21)
    - "Some Facts about the Foundation for Economic Education,", undated. (Folder 83: 22)
    - "Breakfast with Dr. Sproul," Gordon, Robert, undated. (Folder 83: 23)
    - "The Study of Freedom,", 1957. (Folder 83: 24)
    - "Industry-Wide Bargaining," Wolman, Leo, 1948. (Folder 83: 25)
  - Foundation for the Study of Treaty Law--Treaty law manual, undated. (Folder 83: 26)
    Proposal
  - Fourth International--"West Coast Longshoremen ...," Thomas, C., 1943. (Folder 83: 27)
  - Frank E. Holman
    - "State Department Half Truths ...,", 1952. (Folder 83: 28)
    - "The Need for ...,", 1955. (Folder 83: 29)
  - Free enterprise seminar--"The Ideological War ...," Crail, Joe, undated. (Folder 83: 30)
  - A Free Europe, Inc.--"Labor and the Soviet System," Szumski, Romuald, undated. (Folder 83: 31)
  - Free Society Association
    - "Decision in South Vietnam,", 1967. (Folder 83: 32)
      Transcripts of an interview with Howard R. Penniman
    - "Force or Freedom ...,", 1966. (Folder 83: 33)
    - "New Student Left,", 1965. (Folder 83: 34)
    - "The State of our Free Society,", 1966. (Folder 83: 35)
      Keynote address by Barry Goldwater
  - Free Tom Mooney United Front Conference--Dreiser, Theodore, undated. (Box-folder 84: 1)
  - Free Venezuela National Anti-Communist Movement Publications--"A Diary ...,", 1959. (Folder 84: 2)
  - Freedom, 1989. (Folder 84: 3)
  - Freedom Club of the First Congregational Church--"Our Constitution ...," Manion, Clarence (Dean), 1952. (Folder 84: 4)
  - Freedom Forum--"California Dynasty of Communism," Prussion, Karl, undated. (Folder 84: 5)
  - Freedoms Foundation--"Twenty-Third Annual National and School Awards,", 1972. (Folder 84: 6)
  - Freedom House--"The Crisis of Freedom," Feder, Jack, and M. A. Jenkins, 1964. (Folder 84: 7)
  - Freedom School--"Flight to Russia," Chodorov, Frank, 1960?. (Folder 84: 8)
  - Freedom School
    - "Executive Session,", 1965. (Folder 84: 9)
    - "Anarchy," Lefevre, Robert, 1959. (Folder 84: 10)
    - "Must We Depend ...," Opitz, Edmund A., and Robert LeFevre, 1962. (Folder 84: 11)
    - "A Rift between Friends in the War of Ideas,", undated. (Folder 84: 12)
    - "What has Government Done to our Money?" Rothbard, Murray N., undated. (Folder 84: 13)
    - "Should We Strengthen the United Nations?" Watts, V. Orval, 1961. (Folder 84: 14)
  - The Freeman--"The Story of the Freeman,", undated. (Folder 84: 15)
  - Frercks, Rudolf, "German Population Policy,", 1938. (Folder 84: 16)
  - Friends Committee on Legislation--"The Life We Take: A Case ...," Thomas, Trevor, 1970. (Folder 84: 17)
  - Friends of Democracy--"Father Coughlin ...,", undated. (Folder 84: 18)
  - Friends of the Soviet Union
    - "White Guard Terrorists in the U.S.A.," Dennen, Leon, undated. (Folder 84: 19)
    - "One Hundred Years in Ten: ...," Heller, A. A., undated. (Folder 84: 20)
  - Friendship Press--"Sense and Nonsense about Race," Alpenfels, Ethel J., undated. (Folder 84: 21)
  - Fries, Amos A., "Communism Unmasked,", 1937. (Folder 84: 22)
  - Fronis, "Top Secret ...,", undated. (Folder 84: 23)
  - Fulton, Lewis, Jr., 1957. (Folder 84: 24)
  - Fulton (Lewis, Jr.) Productions, "A Gatt in Your Ribs,", 1956. (Folder 84: 25)
  - Fund for the Republic
    - "Economic Power and the Free Society ...," Berle, A. A., Jr., undated. (Folder 84: 26)
    - "Foreign Policy and the Press," Bingham, Barry, undated. (Folder 84: 27)
    - "The U.S., Cuba, and Latin America," Benitez, Jaime, 1961. (Folder 84: 28)
    - "Union Constitutions," Bromwich, Leo, 1959. (Folder 84: 29)
    - "The Corporation and the Republic," Buchanan, Scott, 1958. (Folder 84: 30)
    - "The Berlin Story,", undated. (Folder 84: 31)
      Programs
    - "Broadcasting ...,", 1959. (Folder 84: 32)
    - Center for the Study of Democratic Institutions, undated. (Folder 84: 33)
  - "Freedom for All," Buck, Pearl S., undated. (Folder 84: 34)
  - "Freedom for India Now!" Buck, Pearl S., and others, 1942. (Folder 84: 35)
  - Fund for the Republic (Box 85)
    - "The Press,", 1961. (Folder 85: 1)
    - "Fair Trial vs. Free Press,", 1965. (Folder 85: 2)
    - "Civil Disobedience," Freeman, Harrop A., and others, undated. (Folder 85: 3)
    - "The Elite and ...," Fulbright, William J., and others, 1963. (Folder 85: 4)
    - "The Fund for the Republic,", 1958. (Folder 85: 5)
    - "The Economic Facts of Life," Galbraith J. Kenneth and Joseph A. Livingston, undated. (Folder 85: 6)
    - "Television,", 1961. (Folder 85: 7)
    - "The American Character,", 1962. (Folder 85: 8)
      Excerpts from remarks
    - "Unions and Union ...," Kerr, Clark, 1957. (Folder 85: 9)
    - "Government ...," Kronstein, Heinrich, 1961. (Folder 85: 10)
    - "Right to Work in Practice," Meyers, Frederic, 1959. (Folder 85: 11)
    - Millis, Walter
      - "The Constitution ...,", 1959. (Folder 85: 12)
      - "Individual Freedom and the Common Defense,", undated. (Folder 85: 13)
      - "War and Revolution Today ...,", 1965. (Folder 85: 14)
    - Mollenhoff, Clark, and Edwin A. Lahey, "Secrecy in ...,", undated. (Folder 85: 15)
    - "The Responsibilities of Television," Murrow, Edward R., undated. (Folder 85: 16)
    - "On Coexistence,", 1965. (Folder 85: 17)
    - "On the Developed ...,", 1965. (Folder 85: 18)
    - "Pacempeace in on Terrorism,", 1965. (Folder 85: 19)
    - "Consumers of Abundance," Piel, George, 1961. (Folder 85: 20)
    - Center for the Study of Democratic Institutions--Reports of the president
      - 1958-1959 (Folder 85: 21)
      - 1959-1960 (Folder 85: 22)
    - "Washington and the Press," Reston, James, 1960?. (Folder 85: 23)
    - "The Public and the Publisher," Roper, Elmo, and Palmer Hoyt, 1960?. (Folder 85: 24)
    - "Science, Scientists ...,", 1963. (Folder 85: 25)
    - "The Television News Commentator," Sevareid, Eric, 1960?. (Folder 85: 26)
    - "How the United States ...," Scheer, Robert, 1965. (Folder 85: 27)
    - "The Photo Journalist," Smith, W. Eugene, and Louis Weiner, 1960?. (Folder 85: 28)
    - "The Soviet Challenge," Stevenson, Adlai E., and Barbara Ward, 1960?. (Folder 85: 29)
    - "Survival and Freedom"--Interviews
      - Mortimer, J. Adler, 1960 (Folder 85: 30)
      - Ashmore, Harry S., undated (Folder 85: 31)
      - Douglas, William O., undated (Folder 85: 32)
      - Eaton, Cyrus S., undated (Folder 85: 33)
      - Fromm, Erich, undated (Folder 85: 34)
      - Huxley, Aldous, undated (Folder 85: 35)
      - Kissinger, Henry A., undated (Folder 85: 36)
      - Lally, Francis J., undated (Folder 85: 37)
      - Niebuhr, Reinhold, undated (Folder 85: 38)
      - Percy, Charles H., undated (Folder 85: 39)
      - Stevenson, Adlai E., undated (Folder 85: 40)
      - Weaver, Sylvester L., Jr., undated (Folder 85: 41)
    - "Pension Funds ...," Tilove, Robert, 1959. (Folder 85: 42)
    - "The Bomb and the Press," Ubell, Earl, and Louis Lyons Livingston, 1960?. (Folder 85: 43)
    - "Segregation ...," Weissbourd, Bernard, 1964. (Folder 85: 44)
    - "Looking Forward: ...," Weisskopf, Walter A., N. Iyer Raghavan, and others, 1966. (Folder 85: 45)
    - "When the World's Peoples ...,", 1965. (Folder 85: 46)
    - "The News from China," White, Theodore H. and John K. Fairbank, 1960?. (Folder 85: 47)
    - "Unmasking the ...,", undated. (Folder 85: 48)
  - Gallahad College--"Why are you in Life?" Pelley, William Dudley, undated. (Box-folder 86: 1)
  - Gardener, Harry J.--"The Super Deceiver ...," Hollenbeck, James, 1942. (Folder 86: 2)
  - Gardener, Ray, "Wanted for Murder ...,", undated. (Folder 86: 3)
  - Gateway Editions--"Oration on the ...," Mirondola, Giovanni Pico Della, 1956. (Folder 86: 4)
  - General Motors--Taylor, Henry J.--Remarks
    - "England Today," "Prewar England not Here," and "How Communism Came to Russia,", 1947-1948. (Folder 86: 5)
    - "Representative Government and Courage vs. Opportunism,", 1946 (Folder 86: 6)
  - George E. Sullivan
    - "Alert American ...,", 1947. (Folder 86: 7)
    - "History's ...,", 1948. (Folder 86: 8)
    - "Taking Away ...,", 1948. (Folder 86: 9)